shsu.edu 2002-12-04

# Sam Houston State University Web Privacy Policy

~ (tilde)  following the website are maintained by university individuals and departments and are not covered by this privacy statement. This site contains links to other sites. Sam Houston State University ( **www.shsu.edu)** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. 

Our site uses forms for students, faculty, staff, and visitors to request information, products, and services. We collect contact information (like email addresses) and unique identifiers (like social security number) for university business such as university registration and/or sending catalogues to potential students. 

We do not use cookies to collect information. ( _Note: A cookie file contains unique information a web site can use to track such things as passwords, lists of pages you've visited, and the date when you last looked at a specific page or to identify your session at a particular web site.)_

If you send us an electronic mail message with a question or comment that contains personally identifying information, or fill out a form that e-mails us this information, we will only use the personally-identifiable information to respond to your request and analyze trends. We may redirect your message to another government agency or person who is in a better position to answer your question. 

For site management functions, information is collected for analysis and [statistical purposes](http://www.shsu.edu/stats/shsu-weekly/). This information is not reported or used in any manner that would reveal personally identifiable information, and will not be released to any outside parties unless legally required to do so in connection with law enforcement investigations or other legal proceedings. 

##  Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

##  Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. 

##  Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact  Computer Services Sam Houston State University PO Box 2449 Huntsville, TX 77341 [helpdesk@shsu.edu](mailto:helpdesk@shsu.edu)

* * *

* * *

**Local time is:**  Wed 04 Dec 2002 02:46:34 PM CST  
**Last modified:**  Wed 16 Feb 2000 04:37:32 PM CST  
**Maintained by the** [[Computer Services](http://www.shsu.edu/~ucs_www/)] [Web Development Team]
